[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Kevins first byline in the film St. Elmos Fire?", "correct_answer": "The Meaning of Life", "incorrect_answers": ["After College", "Fluff nFold", "Afraid of Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How will you say I Love You in Filipino?", "correct_answer": "Mahal Kita", "incorrect_answers": ["Ikaw Na Nga", "Sino Ka", "Hindi Ko Alam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Neon?", "correct_answer": "Ne", "incorrect_answers": ["No", "Nn", "N"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Johnny Storm, a member of the Fantastic Four, goes by what moniker?", "correct_answer": "The Human Torch", "incorrect_answers": ["Lava Man", "Sparky", "Flash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What six times winner of the Mr. Olympia crown is featured in  Pumping Iron  ?", "correct_answer": "Arnold Schwarzenegger", "incorrect_answers": ["Charles Atlas", "Jackie Chan", "Hulk Hogan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Christianity, besides black magic, there is also white magic.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Sydneys mothers name in the movie Scream?", "correct_answer": "Maureen", "incorrect_answers": ["Riley", "Penny", "Dorothy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name is given to Rockys new dog in the 2006 film Rocky Balboa?", "correct_answer": "Punchy", "incorrect_answers": ["Looney", "Mickey", "Bubkis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the typical lifespan of the cheetah?", "correct_answer": "10-20 years", "incorrect_answers": ["25-40 years", "15-25 years", "5-10 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Friday the 13th, when Alice discovers a snake in the cabin and yells for Bill, what does Bill stop doing to come help her?", "correct_answer": "chopping weeds", "incorrect_answers": ["swimming", "chopping wood", "painting"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As this is the closest planet to the Sun, its temperatures at the surface range between -300 and 800 F (hot enough for lead to melt).", "correct_answer": "Mercury", "incorrect_answers": ["Neptune", "Pluto", "Venus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The summit ridge of Mount Everest marks the border between which two Asian countries?", "correct_answer": "China and Nepal", "incorrect_answers": ["India and China", "Nepal and India", "China and Georgia"]}]